Joel Bargen

Objective

Hardworking employee with customer service, multitasking and time management abilities. Devoted to giving every customer a positive and memorable experience. More than two years of technical support with positive reviews from managers and those I've assisted throughout my time.

Experience

Ameritas Life Insurance | Lincoln, NE

May 2022 - Present

IT Intern - Endpoint Services

- Prepare, deploy, and provide basic break/fix support for PC equipment and printers
- Document, track, escalate, and attain resolution of incidents and service requests
- Execute technology moves within the building and assist with disposal of retired equipment
- Mentor and train new interns within the support team to more efficiently complete our job

Centennial Public School | Utica, NE

May 2019 - June 2020

IT Intern

- Observed and learned how to maintain and make basic repairs on various hardware devices
- Completed basic repairs on laptops (replacing keyboards/monitors)
- Troubleshoot various technological issues reported by other employees

Cornerstone Bank | York, NE

June 2018 – August 2018

IT Intern

- Shadowed full-time employee and learned how to perform basic hardware troubleshooting
- Aided mentor in replacing older models of technology with newer models
- Participated in updating and documenting technology inventory at all branch locations

Skills & abilities

- Proficient in verbal and written communication
- Problem solver, critical thinker, highly motivated, leader and professional
- C, C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and SQL

Education

University of Nebraska-Lincoln | Lincoln, NE

Expected May 2024

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

- GPA: 3.78
- Dean's List: Fall 2020, Spring 2021, Spring 2022, Fall 2022, Spring 2023, and Fall 2023
- Relevant Coursework: Software Security in Practice & Data and Network Security